<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Amanda&#39;s sick website</title>
    <link>http://example.org/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Amanda&#39;s sick website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Amanda Ernar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 12:55:04 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reverie</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/posts/reverie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 12:55:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/posts/reverie/</guid>
      <description>Creation and destruction, death and rebirth.
Billions of years ago, the Great Creator gave birth to our beloved world. He sculpted man from clay and wove our rivers, hills, and trees into our battered planet using His divine breath.
Or did was the Great Creator just some sort of myth?
That spine-chilling question&amp;rsquo;s been plagueing humanity for centuries. And I, a
 I remember falling asleep that night and never waking up, opening my eyes to a ceaseless horror unraveling itself before my eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/posts/monster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 23:16:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/posts/monster/</guid>
      <description>Whoever fights monsters should see to it that in the process he does not become a monster. And when you look long into an abyss, the abyss also looks into you.&amp;quot; (Beyond Good and Evil, 146)
This is one of the aspects of Nietzsche that is easily overlooked by people who want to see him as simply nihilistic and destructive.
For Nietzsche, the construction of the self is not a religious act, an obligation, or an act of submission to nature, as variously seen by &amp;lsquo;moralities&amp;rsquo; &amp;ndash; it is an art form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butterflies and Blue</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/posts/butterflies-and-blue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 13:42:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/posts/butterflies-and-blue/</guid>
      <description>Famous scientists like Sir Isaac Newton have been fascinated by the color blue in nature. It&amp;rsquo;s incredibly rare and is absolutely beautiful, but why do they only rarely exist in nature? Well, we&amp;rsquo;ll have to look into what pigment is. Pigment is a thing that is released from an organism&amp;rsquo;s body due to the things it eats. Flamingoes get their pink pigment from the crustaceans (shrimp, crabs) they eat. Spoiler: there really aren&amp;rsquo;t any organisms that make blue pigment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faust</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/posts/faust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 21:41:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/posts/faust/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
You couldn&amp;rsquo;t possibly understand why I did what I did that fateful day. I&amp;rsquo;d probably rot in hell for the rest of eternity for that. But for now, I felt nothing at all. Absolutely nothing, not even the slightest bit of regret. Death really was strange.
A pity, as it was. Life, death, love, hatred; these conceptions were so utterly human, yet so beautiful&amp;hellip;.
As my rotting corpse was set ablaze, I decided to try and revise my answers to the questions I had asked back when my heart still pounded with life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/posts/generalizing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 21:41:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/posts/generalizing/</guid>
      <description>The world&amp;rsquo;s smartest folks know how to do this thing really well: generalizing different words of wisdom. Generalizing big ideas is very simple! Let me give you an example. In biology class, students learn about food webs and food chains. They also learn about the energy transfer and how it decreases by 10% at each step of the food pyramid due to more energy being spent, and the exponential decrease in energy being consumed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hands</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/posts/hands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 21:41:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/posts/hands/</guid>
      <description>My hands
Battered, Bruised
Have been torn, Have been used, Have been tortured, Have been stepped on
They have removed weeds, They have drawn pictures, They have turned pages, They have served supper
There is a scar on the right side of my right hand. There is a blister on the left side of my left palm.
My hands can write, My hands can tie knots, My hands can play the piano, My hands can feel pain</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
