<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amanda Ernar</title>
    <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Amanda Ernar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 10:39:09 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>hhh</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/hhh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 10:39:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/hhh/</guid>
      <description>To-do:
 Get poetry analysis whatnot done Finish children&amp;rsquo;s books with pictures Set up good system for completing work, set specific time to take breaks and piano etc. practice vim  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excuses</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/excuses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 13:56:19 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/excuses/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s very human of us to make excuses for ourselves, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that it&amp;rsquo;s a good thing to do. Making excuses is disrespectful and it prevents your confronter from getting their point across. When confronted, the best thing you can do is just apologize and admit that you&amp;rsquo;re wrong. If you truly believe that they are not correct in the issue they&amp;rsquo;ve addressed, politely state your opinion in a clear way for them to understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being Early</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/being-early/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 10:02:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/being-early/</guid>
      <description>Always prepare the night before something. Especially if the next day is a school day. Set your alarm clock, layout some clean clothes, and set up your zoom station or whatever. Always be twenty minutes early. Why be early? I thought it doesn’t do you any good to be early!
Well, not quite. Your blood pressure and physical wellbeing deteriorate as you are in a rush. Your heart beats out of your chest and you might even start sweating nervously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 13:23:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/trust/</guid>
      <description>They say trust is like an eraser because it gets smaller every time you use it up. I agree. Trust gives individuals power, and it&amp;rsquo;s more valuable than gold. But by &amp;ldquo;using&amp;rdquo; trust, what do they mean? Well, lying. If you didn&amp;rsquo;t assume that then you&amp;rsquo;re dumb lol
It&amp;rsquo;s hard to trust people with a history of lying. You all know the tale of the boy who cried wolf. Aesop, am I right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 14:25:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/reflection/</guid>
      <description>12.2.20 Move fast. If you can move quicker, then do it, especially if you have priorities. Be efficient. Learn in an efficient manner. Use your brian; if something isn&amp;rsquo;t worth doing, then don&amp;rsquo;t do it. Plan. Have an aim/goal for the day. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re hanging out with your friends, coding, doing martial arts, try to always have a goal. Planning is the only way you&amp;rsquo;re going to get anywhere in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:46:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>Amanda Ernar has acquired many skills during her lifespan of less than twenty years. She has qualified for the Los Angeles Regional Spelling Bee when she was just in the fourth grade and has always thought of herself as an &amp;ldquo;excellent speller&amp;rdquo;. Lately, Ernar has been working on a net-worth tracking application that would be handled by a single database. She has astounding grades, nice hair, and a beautiful piano. Oh, yeah, she can play piano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butterflies and Blue</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/butterflies-and-blue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 13:42:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/butterflies-and-blue/</guid>
      <description>Famous scientists like Sir Isaac Newton have been fascinated by the color blue in nature. It&amp;rsquo;s incredibly rare and is absolutely beautiful, but why do they only rarely exist in nature? Well, we&amp;rsquo;ll have to look into what pigment is. Pigment is a thing that is released from an organism&amp;rsquo;s body due to the things it eats. Flamingoes get their pink pigment from the crustaceans (shrimp, crabs) they eat. Spoiler: there really aren&amp;rsquo;t any organisms that make blue pigment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One Thousand Times Rule</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/1-thousand-times-rule/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 21:53:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/1-thousand-times-rule/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever heard or read somewhere about the 1,000 times rule? Well, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s actually pretty simple to understand. Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve heard the saying, &amp;ldquo;If you could do _____ one thousand times in the future, how would you do it?&amp;rdquo; Let&amp;rsquo;s say you&amp;rsquo;re driving your car and running a bit late for your job interview. Suddenly, your phone starts buzzing like crazy and plays a song by Mariah Carey: your interviewer is calling you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/generalizing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 21:41:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/generalizing/</guid>
      <description>The world&amp;rsquo;s smartest folks know how to do this thing really well: generalizing different words of wisdom. Generalizing big ideas is very simple! Let me give you an example. In biology class, students learn about food webs and food chains. They also learn about the energy transfer and how it decreases by 10% at each step of the food pyramid due to more energy being spent, and the exponential decrease in energy being consumed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sagan&#39;s Journal</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/sagans-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 15:31:28 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/sagans-journal/</guid>
      <description>It hadn’t rained in thirty years.
“It hadn’t snowed, either. It stopped snowing around seventy years ago, and it stopped raining just thirty years ago. The world was going to end. I hadn’t done anything in my twenty-four years of living, and it was quite dry nowadays, you know? According to several sources, you guys thought that by the year 3000 we would have flying cars and stuff. Well, you were wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ancient India</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/ancient-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/ancient-india/</guid>
      <description>India has evolved fascinatingly throughout its existence. It has been through many civil wars, governments, and periods. Ancient India was an astonishingly intelligent civilization, for it had come up with many revolutionary inventions. Some of these include the field of medicine, the decimal system, fables, and the game of chess. India has always been one of the most advanced civilizations, and this essay will explain why.
One celebrated conqueror of Ancient India was Chandragupta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Woodsong</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/from-woodsong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/from-woodsong/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;From Woodsong&amp;rdquo; by Gary Paulsen tells a heartwarming story concerning the day he encounters a bear. The tale commences when Paulsen is removing burned food from his home one beautiful July morning. He spots a large male bear tearing his trash can apart. Paulsen then provokes the bear by hurling shoots and branches at it, and the animal charged. The bear&amp;rsquo;s intimidating figure hovered above Paulsen for a good minute or two, sniffing him up and down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine and the Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/quarantine-and-the-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandaernar.github.io/blog/posts/quarantine-and-the-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been about a few months since the beginning of the national lockdown. So far, there have been 6,570,362 cases reported worldwide. There are about ten times that amount, so that would be 60 million cases. I&amp;rsquo;m kind of scared about going outside. 2020 has been a terrible year so far.
These are a few things that have happened since January first:
 The novel coronavirus of 2019 has spread to many countries World War 3 threatened to start Australia is burning (koalas are dying) A helicopter crash kills Kobe and Gianna Bryant COVID-19 is considered a pandemic Dow plunges almost 3,000 points Tokyo postpones Olympics The United States officially impeaches President Trump Officers brutally murder George Floyd, sparking uprisings in Minneapolis Black Lives Matter comes back due to black deaths Criminals loot homes, banks, and luxury stores Protesters burn down cities ALL TOILET PAPER IS GONE Dolphins are in the Venice Canals due to no pollution  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
